Caleb Sanders

Full-Stack Web Developer

(530) 526-9189 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/caleb-sanders-wd/ | 97caleb.sanders@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://calebsanders.herokuapp.com/

Professional Summary

Excellent work history in positions requiring responsibility, initiative, accuracy and confidentiality. Ability to interface effectively with management. Hard working and dedicated to meet the standards expected for the job. Main area of expertise focused around the design and development of websites.

Technical Skills

CSS, HTML5, JavaScript, C#, NodeJS + ExpressJS Java, Android, ES6, AngularJS, React MongoDB, ASP.NET MVC, Ruby

Experience

DealerSocket

Neumont Collaborative Project Externship Draper, UT | April 2018 – Present

- ❖ Developing a QA Tool for the Data Analytics team. The tool will be used to compare records from two different databases after data conversion. The process will the company hundreds of thousands of dollars.
- * Tribal D, Inc. Native American Self Governance

Neumont Collaborative Project Externship North Salt Lake, UT | January 2018 – March 2018

Provided extra assistance to the team at the company. Added new item types for the company's database. Created new applications to improve user experience. In the process saved the other developers from hours of extra work.

Student Ambassador

Neumont College of Computer Science Salt Lake City, UT | February 2017 – September 2017

❖ The purpose as an ambassador was to welcome prospective students considering enrollment. Including answering any questions a family may have as well as promoting the school to the families.

Project Highlights

Capstone Project – Frank Florez House Cleaning

Designed and built a fully-fledged e-commerce site for a previous employer. The site allows the user to easily generate a service order for house cleaning online. Developed using NodeJS/ExpressJS, AngularJS, EJS, and Google OAuth.

Advanced Web Scripting Final – Activity Hunt

This SPA serves to allow users to find activities to do regardless of the weather outside. The purpose of this application is to solve the issue of boredom experience in everyday lives. Developed using AngularJS and Google Maps API.

Web Based Software Projects – Talon

This application serves as a stats tracker for the popular video game Overwatch by Blizzard Entertainment. This application implements an unofficial API for all player data. Developed using ASP.NET MVC and SQL.

Education

Bachelors of Science, Web Design and Development

Neumont College of Computer Science

Salt Lake City, UT | October 2015 – August, 2018